Dongsuk.
Why do we make it so complicated?
We can just kill them there.
Are you an idiot?
If we do it there and wake up that spider.
how will we take the mana crystal?
I don't care what his nickname is.
An E-Rank hunter and a D-Rank hunter
without combat experience
will never defeat that Boss.
We wait for that spider
to eat them and fall asleep again.
Then we can take the mana crystal out.
Do we blast it open again
with flash magic?
That'll wake up the spider again.
There's a small path above the cave.
We go down from there.
I see.
You are a genius. Dongsuk.
But will it fall asleep?
If it doesn't. we'll have to take it down.
That guy's name is Yoo Jinho. right?
Did you see his equipment?
Just the sword and shield alone
are worth hundreds of millions.
If we can't take the mana crystal.
we'll take his belongings instead.
Let me see which wealthy family he's from.
At least we should attend the funeral.
By the way.
the noise we made when sealing the road
must have infuriated that Boss a lot.
Kyuhwan.
Do you think you can
kill that beast by yourself?
How could I possibly do that?
Honestly. me neither.
Boss in Dungeon cannot be underestimated.
In other words. those two
can't possibly leave there alive.
Please wait.
At least a B-Rank hunter
can defeat a C-Rank Boss alone.
Or a top-tier C-Rank hunter.
Jinwoo. you can't do it...
Let's find a way to get out.
Jinho is right.
Even though I've had a second awakening
and leveled up.
I am still very weak now.
The Venom-Fanged Kasaka
in the instance dungeon
should be D-Rank.
That Golem Boss is
probably D-Rank or lower.
This Boss is worlds apart from those.
But why?
I can't feel any pressure
that would frustrate me.
I've become strong enough
to no longer fear a C-Rank Boss.
My current level is 18.
Against a C-Rank Boss...
I have a chance of fighting it.
Hunters are called hunters
because the real hunt begins now.
You've worked hard.
Government officials. media.
and energy-related groups.
Having meetings with them for days
in a row is truly exhausting.
I've never been good at
beating around the bush.
I heard you have no plans coming up.
If possible. could I ask you
for a sparring match?
Perhaps it could change your mood.
I am already a withered veteran...
But how can I refuse when
a young person seeks my guidance?
Its hide is very hard.
Its attack is surprisingly powerful.
If I took one hit. I would be dead.
That kind of move...
He is definitely not an E-Rank hunter.
Who is he?
Is he...
a False Ranker?
I've heard about them.
Very few hunters can control their magic
power to deliberately get a lower rating.
They are called False Rankers.
And they are usually
psychopaths who take pleasure in killing.
Why did I come here?
Dad...
Damn it.
Its hide is too hard.
I can't harm it at all.
My fatigue...
If it keeps increasing.
it will slow me down.
I need to get rid of it
before that happens.
Paralysis and drain.
This dagger's special
abilities are key to victory.
It'll take effect if I hit its weak spot.
That's the spot!
Acid.
It had this trick too.
Tough hide and the strong acid.
It's tougher to deal with than I expected.
If this continues.
I have no chance of winning.
I have to close the distance between us.
The new skill Dash.
Use this move to get to it.
If it doesn't work once.
Then I'll try again!
He's so fast.
But can his vitality hold up?
What on earth is he planning?
Faster.
Even faster.
Almost there...
Jinwoo!
Thankfully I didn't claim
the rewards for the daily quest.
Otherwise. I can't even
imagine the consequences.
Unbelievable.
He defeated the Boss all by himself.
There's no mistake.
He's a False Ranker.
How much is this worth?
Well...
Sir.
Do you need me to help
you with the magic gem?
I can carry the luggage too.
Have some water. sir.
Thank...
Why is he suddenly calling me that?
Please take a rest. sir.
I'll mine the mana crystal.
What's with this kid?
They are still alive.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thank you for your guidance.
I've relaxed a lot.
Thank you.
You are amazing. president.
There's no sign of decline in your skills.
No. I'm no longer as good as I used to be.
Jinchul. your moves have improved.
It seems you've done a lot of training.
Training can't increase hunters' level.
but it can improve their skills.
Hmm.
Don't take pride in the hunter's strength.
Having a physical and mind training
is indeed important.
Especially if you're going to
a dangerous place like a dungeon.
After all. in such places.
you see the worst of people.
Is the Boss dead?
This spider is all bark and no bite.
What a crap.
With his equipment. defeating
a C-Rank Boss isn't impossible.
Even so. it's embarrassing
to lose to a D-Rank hunter.
Dongsuk. what should we do?
What else?
Yoo Jinho.
I looked you up because of
your expensive equipment.
You are no ordinary person.
The president of
Yoojin Construction. Yoo Myunghan.
He's your dad. right?
So what?
I'll give you a chance.
Kill Sung Jinwoo.
Eh?
You know what we do. right?
We kill those useless ones
who just come to fill numbers
to take the spoils for ourselves.
Yoo Jinho.
I want you to be our accomplice.
If you do. I'll spare you.
How can I...
That young master killed a C-Rank BOSS
on his own with that equipment.
It'll be troublesome
if that equipment has special effects.
If you refuse. you can die together.
What's wrong?
What's there to hesitate about?
No one will know what happened here.
Are you afraid of that E-Rank trash?
Huh?
What?
Are you taking his side?
Dongsuk. what do we do now?
You start with the weaker one.
Have you two
ever killed people?
Urgent quest?
What's going on?
Pay attention here.
Take this!
Jinwoo!
Heejin.
Long time no see.
What's going on
at the White Tiger Guild lately?
Nothing much.
It's the same as usual.
How about your Hunters Guild. Gina?
The same as usual too.
By the way. you went to Hunter Cha's
A-Rank dungeon training. right?
How did it go?
It was awesome.
It ended in an instant.
Those A-Rank magic beasts
we struggled with
were instantly taken down by her.
She defeated enemies effortlessly.
Needless to say. we were surprised.
Kihoon was quite shocked.
Because his goal was to
become the next Captain.
Someone who works as hard
as he would be more shocked.
What about your Kim Chul?
Doesn't he have the same goal?
He also wants to be the Captain.
He's not a bad guy...
That says it all.
But after all. we are pretty lucky
as we are able to join large guilds
like Hunters Guild and White Tiger Guild.
That's true.
Hmm.
After all. there are ominous
rumors in some places.
Ominous rumors?
The teams with
an abnormally high casualty rate.
Something like that.
Yoo Jinho. he's dead.
How can you do that?
How could I forget?
This is a place that believes
in the survival of the fittest.
a place full of violence and deceit.
How could I...
I see.
I've become numb.
careless. arrogant. and deluded.
Enemies.
The system is forcing me to kill people.
Does that mean it doesn't want me to die?
This is neither coincidence nor kindness.
The system needs me.
I must be strong.
Thank goodness.
Hey. he's still alive.
I see.
The system is using me.
And I am using the system too.
Hey. Kyuhwan. don't hold back.
How could I forget?
The weak will have
everything taken from them.
This place is just like that.
You understand it very well.
The Weakest Hunter of All Mankind.
That means...
You are also mentally prepared. right?
What?
What are you saying?
I'm asking
whether you are also
prepared to be hunted.
Dongsuk. let me do it.
Buddy.
It seems like you don't quite
understand the situation.
Mentally prepared to be hunted?
What can a boastful E-Rank hunter do?
The Weakest Hunter of All Mankind.
The first one.
Jun... Juntae.
No way.
When did he have a weapon in his hand?
Where did he hide it?
Even if he was careless.
Juntae was still a D-Rank hunter.
How could an E-Rank hunter
manage to kill him?
I killed someone...
I killed...
I am following the system's instructions.
but the fact is
I killed someone.
But if I don't. I will be the one to die.
There's no turning back now.
Since only the strong can survive...
Go to hell!
- Die!
Huh?
How can an E-Rank hunter have such skills?
You bad guy...
Kyuhwan!
Yes.
Take this!
So strong.
I think he's even stronger
than he was when fighting the Boss.
You wiped out
my team members in an instant.
You've been hiding your ability.
You defeated the Boss too. didn't you?
But even if I'm also a C-Rank hunter.
I'm not the same as them.
Enhancement!
Even if he is as strong as a demon.
he must be exhausted after
fighting the Boss and five hunters.
He relies on his speed and
the special abilities of that dagger.
But my enhanced body is as hard as steel.
Your dagger
won't work on me.
Take this!
Captain Hwang.
You are very strong.
But let me tell you something.
That is...
I am always leveling up.
What... What happened?
He... He knocked me to the ground.
This guy
is no way an E-Rank hunter.
Wait! Don't kill me.
Please spare me.
Money... I'll give you money.
All the Mana Crystals and Magic Gems here.
You keep all of them.
Is it not enough?
I understand.
I'll double the money for you.
- I'll pay...
- Three times...
You tried to kill me three times.
Are you begging me to spare your life?
Stop... stop!
Do you think you can get away with this?
No one will know what
happened in the dungeon.
You said it.
Bad guy!
Do you know who my brother is...
After the Boss dies.
the dungeon will begin to close.
Let's get out quickly.
Hmm...
All C-Rank hunters have perished.
The survivors are
a D-Rank hunter and an E-Rank hunter?
That's right.
Well...
You.
Yes.
That sword in your hand
is the Claymore Kallion
from the Maya Company. right?
It just hit the market.
Yeah.
I didn't know there'd be rewards too.
Skill: Murderous Intent.
All abilities are halved?
I see.
If you are using that equipment.
I can understand.
You defeated the Boss alone
and this E-Rank hunter hid away. right?
Thank you for your help today.
The investigation ends here.
Well...
Thank you. sir.
Hmm.
Is something wrong?
No.
I was just thinking
thankfully I had her take an umbrella.